vserv.mobi 2014-06-26

# Vserv.mobi Privacy Policy - Vserv.mobi

Last updated: 13/01/2014  

Introduction  
Information collected by Vserv  
Information usage  
Information sharing  
Cookie placement  
Opt Out  
Amendment of Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Vserv is a Global Mobile Ad Network and is into business of Mobile Advertising through its Mobile Ad Serving Platform.This document covers the privacy policy of Vserv which applies to the WAPS/APPS on Mobile where we serve ads.  
Our Privacy Policy explains how we and some of the companies we work with collect, use, share and protect information in relation to our mobile services, web site, and any software provided on or in connection with Vserv services (collectively, the “ **Service** “), and your choices about the collection and use of your information.

### Information collected by Vserv

We may collect certain information from the user’s device during ad serving/interaction, which may include following:

  * User Agent
  * Network provider
  * Internet (IP) address
  * Device identifier
  * Media Access Control (MAC) address,
  * Geo location
  * The content type of the ad / genre
  * Media type of the ad ( text, image, video)
  * User interaction events, post click activity of user

We may also partner with Data Providers who provide us information which they automatically collect a variety of information associated with your use of your device and our products and services, some of which may be associated with you or another user on your account, which we can help us to improve relevancy of ads and better ads experience. Data about you collected by them is in accordance with their own specific privacy policies and subject to their own applicable legal terms and conditions. We do not intend to use the information provided by them to us for the purpose other than serving you with interest-based ads.

**Children**. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 18 years of age. If you allow a child to use your device or our services, you should be aware that their personal information could be collected as described in this policy.

### Information usage

We may use the information we collect to:  
Display relevant ads based on user deducted interests.  
Provide filtering options to our affiliates (Developers/Publishers/Associates)  
To provide targeting options for Advertisers.  
To help advertisers to avoid serving ads which user has already seen/interacted with/acted upon.  
We may also use your information for internal purposes, such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our services & content.

None of the “ _Personally identifiable information_ ” (PII) collected from the user will be used for the purpose other than mentioned under this policy.

### Information sharing

  * We may share your information with Advertisers, Developers or other affiliates which will not have any of your PII.
  * We may share the information with an Expert Partner for analysis of data which can helps us in displaying relevant ads and targeting.
  * While sharing information, we will ensure proper hashing/encryption of PII. We use a variety of safeguards to protect the information we collect about you.
  * We will provide user information where necessary to comply with the law, such as disclosure of your information to a law enforcement agency for your safety or the safety of others, or when compelled by subpoena or other legal process.
  * We may share your information to provide, maintain and improve our Services.

### Cookies placement

Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that helps us to improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits.  
However as per our current policy we do not place any cookies to collect user information.

### Opt Out

To provide better User Ad experience, we have globally partnered with many Telecom Operators for offering advertisements through AudiencePro, which will provide us information like your location, age-group, profile information, preferences from operators and which will help us in delivering relevant ads on your devices.

Vserv shall continue to comply with the provisions of its Privacy Policy for any data received. Further, this information is never stored by Vserv, and remains secure with your Telecom Operator which remains secure at their respective data centers. We have agreed with them not to share information with any third party, and will be used solely to provide you more relevant advertising experience

Vserv provides you an Opt out option, If you still wish to opt out of AudiencePro and stop being targeted for relevant ads, you can visit this [link](http://www.vserv.mobi/audiencepro/opt-out/). At this point, we do not capture any information like web pages visited by user etc. and we do not place any cookies to collect user information.

Please keep in mind that, to the extent we have already disclosed information about you to third parties before you opt out, we cannot order such third parties to delete that information.

NOTE: This does not restrict us from showing generic ads to you.

### Amendment of Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. The latest Privacy Policy is available on our main website: [www.vserv.mobi](http://www.vserv.mobi/). Please check our Privacy Policy regularly to stay up to date.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator: [legal@vserv.mobi](mailto:legal@vserv.mobi)
